Hi, Sachin.
In your introductory comments, you referenced ongoing analysis looking at correlating CDOX to
outcomes, and that you would use that for the conversation with the regulator. So I guess two
linked questions. One, will you comment about data when you have it? And B, what conversations
have you had with the regulator around using that analysis to try and accelerate the buy market
driven file? Thank you.
Yeah.
Yeah, Sachin. So we have the previous interactions that Avidity had with FDA
on what would be required in this Phase 1b, Phase 2 study to enable filing.
So we're very clear on what the FDA is looking for.
And, I mean, if you think about it, the way the FDA thinks about this is we know that
Dux4 is impacted in this disease.
How is circulating KHDL-C correlating with Dux4?
How is that relating to creatine kinase?
And how is all of this relating ultimately to muscle function as best as we can determine
in the patient set that we have?
So we have that data.
We're analyzing the biopsy data that we have as well from the patients in the trial, and
then putting that all together to take it to the FDA.
What I can say is the data that we've seen thus far gives us, we believe we have reason
to have the discussion with the FDA and to make the case.
We can't.
I can't guarantee that we will win the case, but I think we have what we think is worthy
of a case that should be made to the FDA for an accelerated filing.
And once we have that meeting, we'll provide further guidance.
Very clear.
Thank you.
We will now take our final question for today.
And the final question comes from the line of Peter Fadalt from BNP Paribas.
Please go ahead.
Yeah, thanks for the follow-up.
Quick one to end for Mukul.
Just on Rapsida.
So the Acuvia trends look great, and I heard your comments about it earlier about don't
expect inflection, but can you help us at all giving us a ballpark split between, you
know, what is bridged versus paid prescriptions right now?
Just any ballpark numbers would be helpful.
Thank you.
Mukul?
Or is it, is this going to be me?
So I think, well, I can take that, Peter.
I wasn't sure if you were directing it to Mukul.
But, you know, on Rapsida, yeah, we're not providing any detailed guidance on the bridging
program.
You know, what I would say is it's in line with what we're doing.
What we've historically seen in terms of getting patients over to paid scripts.